{
    "CreateOrderWithGivenTestCode": {
        "ValidateOnly": false,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 0,
        "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "12/11/2024",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "DDD",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1980",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "NON_FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "125149",
            "Code": "411475",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "LastName": "1975"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "123937",
                "Code": "1234567894",
                "FirstName": "MP",
                "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "B125",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithGivenAccountNumber": {
        "ValidateOnly": false,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 0,
        "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3332",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "12/11/2024",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "DDD",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1980",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "NON_FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "125149",
            "Code": "411475",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "LastName": "1975"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "123937",
                "Code": "1234567894",
                "FirstName": "MP",
                "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "B125",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithMultipleTests": {
        "ValidateOnly": false,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "j3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/11/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "DDD",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "TEST",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "MiddleName": "T",
                    "PatientId": "123",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1980",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "125149",
                    "Code": "411475",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "LastName": "1975"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "123937",
                        "Code": "1234567894",
                        "FirstName": "MP",
                        "LastName": "0322"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "B125",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "0009",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    } 
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithWrongSpecimen": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "j3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/31/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "04:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "562",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "OK",
                    "FirstName": "NO",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "888",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/10/1970",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "123901",
                    "Code": "410340",
                    "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
                    "LastName": "1080"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "123937",
                        "Code": "1234567894",
                        "FirstName": "MP",
                        "LastName": "0322"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "4931",
                        "Code": "1184762718",
                        "FirstName": "DAVID",
                        "LastName": "30159"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "J148",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 04:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 19712,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C309",
                                "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes",
                                "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C522",
                                "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                                "AnswerText": "> = 76 years old and total PSA > = 4 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C171",
                                "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                                "AnswerText": "No prior biopsy",
                                "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C169",
                                "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                                "AnswerText": "Nodule",
                                "TestName": "DRE Results",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C310",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                                "AnswerText": "76 years or older and PSA greater than 4 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C311",
                                "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, the 4Kscore Test is medically reasonable and necessary for the biopsy decision.  The patient DOES NOT have factors indicating a biopsy should occur.",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C263",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                                "AnswerText": "Confirmed PSA > 3.0 ng mL",
                                "TestName": "Patient History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C264",
                                "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                                "TestName": "Other",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C270",
                                "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                                "AnswerText": "YES",
                                "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C465",
                                "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                                "AnswerText": "55",
                                "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithAgeLessThanRequired": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "j3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/31/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "04:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "154",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "MIO",
                    "FirstName": "LIO",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "259",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/10/1981",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "125149",
                    "Code": "411475",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "LastName": "1975"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "136942",
                        "Code": "6787665454",
                        "FirstName": "test by taj",
                        "LastName": "5544"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "J148",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 04:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 21333,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C309",
                                "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes",
                                "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C522",
                                "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                                "AnswerText": "> = 76 years old and total PSA > = 4 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C171",
                                "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, Negative",
                                "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C169",
                                "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                                "AnswerText": "Nodule",
                                "TestName": "DRE Results",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C310",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                                "AnswerText": "45-54 years and PSA greater than 2 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C311",
                                "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, the 4Kscore Test is medically reasonable and necessary for the biopsy decision.  The patient DOES NOT have factors indicating a biopsy should occur.",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C263",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                                "AnswerText": "Confirmed Persistent and Significant Rise in PSA",
                                "TestName": "Patient History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C264",
                                "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                                "TestName": "Other",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C270",
                                "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                                "AnswerText": "YES",
                                "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C465",
                                "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                                "AnswerText": "174",
                                "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-31T04:36:47.182611-05:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-31T04:39:26.3195557-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithNoSpecimen": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "j3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "0",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/31/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "04:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "654",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "OK",
                    "FirstName": "OK",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "99",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/05/1972",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "123901",
                    "Code": "410340",
                    "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
                    "LastName": "1080"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "4931",
                        "Code": "1184762718",
                        "FirstName": "DAVID",
                        "LastName": "30159"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "J148",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 04:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C309",
                                "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes",
                                "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C522",
                                "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                                "AnswerText": "> = 76 years old and total PSA > = 4 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C171",
                                "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, Negative",
                                "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C169",
                                "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                                "AnswerText": "Nodule",
                                "TestName": "DRE Results",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C310",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                                "AnswerText": "76 years or older and PSA greater than 4 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C311",
                                "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, the 4Kscore Test is medically reasonable and necessary for the biopsy decision.  The patient DOES NOT have factors indicating a biopsy should occur.",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C263",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                                "AnswerText": "Confirmed PSA > 3.0 ng mL",
                                "TestName": "Patient History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C264",
                                "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                                "TestName": "Other",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C270",
                                "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                                "AnswerText": "YES",
                                "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C465",
                                "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                                "AnswerText": "36",
                                "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-31T05:12:28.3834785-05:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-31T05:14:30.0859645-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithDOCinPast": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 0,
        "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "01/01/2000",
        "TimeOfCollection": "",
        "Priority": "STAT",
        "STATPriorityIncidentId": "2",
        "AlternateDateCollected": "",
        "SpecimenComments": "",
        "Comments": "",
        "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
        "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-24T00:00:00",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "SurgicalNumber": "",
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTRATHAKUR",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "RAJ",
            "FirstName": "RAJ",
            "MiddleName": "",
            "PatientId": "4444",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1980",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "123901",
            "Code": "410340",
            "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
            "LastName": "1080"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "0134",
                "DateCollected": "01/01/2000 ",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderedTestCode": "",
                "ParentTestCode": "",
                "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                "OrderTestAnswers": [
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C042",
                        "QuestionText": "IS PATIENT PREGNANT?",
                        "AnswerText": "",
                        "TestName": "PREGNANT",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "0134"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "SpecimenID": 0,
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
        "FlaggedTests": [],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithStateRestricted": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3337",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/31/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "03:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "MIGHTY",
                    "FirstName": "RIGHT",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "154",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/10/1972",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "9602",
                    "Code": "1194982579",
                    "FirstName": "ADESUWA",
                    "LastName": "OKESANYA"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "21477",
                        "Code": "1407839418",
                        "FirstName": "SURINDERJEET",
                        "LastName": "SANDHU"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "B456",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 03:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 1674,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-31T03:13:46.514014-05:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-31T03:16:47.4820403-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithRetiredTest": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/24/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-24T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJLTRATHAKUR",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "1111",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "RAJ",
                    "FirstName": "RAJ",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "3333",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1990",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "123901",
                    "Code": "410340",
                    "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
                    "LastName": "1080"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "123937",
                        "Code": "1234567894",
                        "FirstName": "MP",
                        "LastName": "0322"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "P598",
                        "DateCollected": "12/24/2024 ",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 20800,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    },
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "PINK",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    },
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [
                    {
                        "Category": "AddSpecimen",
                        "SummaryText": "User confirmed :The numbers of specimens entered is greater than the initial count"
                    }
                ],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithClarifyTest": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/31/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "04:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "655",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "MY",
                    "FirstName": "MY",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "156",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/12/1967",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "4931",
                    "Code": "1184762718",
                    "FirstName": "DAVID",
                    "LastName": "30159"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "125149",
                        "Code": "411475",
                        "FirstName": "Test",
                        "LastName": "1975"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "C999",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 04:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 1,
                                "FormatType": 13,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "O027",
                                "QuestionText": "Clarify Test",
                                "AnswerText": "455",
                                "TestName": "Clarify Test",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "C999"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-31T04:58:43.2333937-05:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-31T05:03:24.1532258-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithMaleTestOnly": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/26/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "05:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-26T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "256",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "MUK",
                    "FirstName": "AHM",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "22",
                    "Gender": "FEMALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/10/1975",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "125149",
                    "Code": "411475",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "LastName": "1975"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "128165",
                        "Code": "1366616484",
                        "FirstName": "WERNER",
                        "LastName": "ANDRADE ORTIZ"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "J148",
                        "DateCollected": "12/26/2024 05:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C309",
                                "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes",
                                "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C522",
                                "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                                "AnswerText": "> = 76 years old and total PSA > = 4 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C171",
                                "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                                "AnswerText": "Not Provided",
                                "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C169",
                                "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                                "AnswerText": "Not Provided",
                                "TestName": "DRE Results",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C310",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                                "AnswerText": "45-54 years and PSA greater than 2 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C311",
                                "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, the 4Kscore Test is medically reasonable and necessary for the biopsy decision.  The patient DOES NOT have factors indicating a biopsy should occur.",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C263",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                                "AnswerText": "Confirmed PSA > 3.0 ng mL,Confirmed Persistent and Significant Rise in PSA",
                                "TestName": "Patient History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C264",
                                "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                                "TestName": "Other",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C270",
                                "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                                "AnswerText": "YES",
                                "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C465",
                                "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                                "AnswerText": "154",
                                "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithFemaleTestOnly": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 0,
        "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "",
        "TimeOfCollection": "04:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
        "AlternateDateCollected": "",
        "SpecimenComments": "",
        "Comments": "",
        "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
        "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "SurgicalNumber": "",
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "555",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "MIN",
            "FirstName": "KIN",
            "MiddleName": "",
            "PatientId": "457",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "12/02/1968",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "123901",
            "Code": "410340",
            "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
            "LastName": "1080"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "125149",
                "Code": "411475",
                "FirstName": "Test",
                "LastName": "1975"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "0327",
                "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 04:00 AM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderedTestCode": "",
                "ParentTestCode": "",
                "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                "TestActionId_TM": 3010,
                "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            },
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "1201",
                "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 04:00 AM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderedTestCode": "",
                "ParentTestCode": "",
                "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "True",
                "AutoAddParentCode": "0327",
                "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                "TestConditionId_TM": 18,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "SpecimenID": 0,
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
        "FlaggedTests": [],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithDuplicateSpecimen": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "2",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/31/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "05:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "582",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "MO",
                    "FirstName": "IO",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "897",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/10/1970",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "125149",
                    "Code": "411475",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "LastName": "1975"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "123937",
                        "Code": "1234567894",
                        "FirstName": "MP",
                        "LastName": "0322"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "0009",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 05:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "2",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithDifferentAccount": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3332",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/11/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "DDD",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "TEST",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "MiddleName": "T",
                    "PatientId": "123",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1980",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "125149",
                    "Code": "411475",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "LastName": "1975"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "123937",
                        "Code": "1234567894",
                        "FirstName": "MP",
                        "LastName": "0322"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "0009",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithProviderInactivePCLFlag": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/24/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-24T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJLTRATHAKUR",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "2222",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    },
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "2222",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "RAJ",
                    "FirstName": "RAJ",
                    "MiddleName": "RAJ",
                    "PatientId": "2222",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1990",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "123581",
                    "Code": "3333333333",
                    "FirstName": "TESTKAREN",
                    "LastName": "TESTPROVIDER"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "123937",
                        "Code": "1234567894",
                        "FirstName": "MP",
                        "LastName": "0322"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "0134",
                        "DateCollected": "12/24/2024 ",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C042",
                                "QuestionText": "IS PATIENT PREGNANT?",
                                "AnswerText": "YES",
                                "TestName": "PREGNANT",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "0134"
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "0002",
                        "DateCollected": "12/24/2024 ",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithPreapprovalPAHFlag": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "1",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "01/07/2025",
                "TimeOfCollection": "03:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "154",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "MILD",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "222",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/03/1985",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "123901",
                    "Code": "410340",
                    "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
                    "LastName": "1080"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "125522",
                        "Code": "2587413695",
                        "FirstName": "nikki",
                        "LastName": "about"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "9680",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 03:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": []
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-31T03:51:16.8027935-05:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-31T03:52:47.5969563-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithDuplicateDUPFlag": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 0,
        "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "2",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "01/07/2025",
        "TimeOfCollection": "06:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
        "AlternateDateCollected": "",
        "SpecimenComments": "",
        "Comments": "",
        "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
        "InitialReceivedDate": "2025-01-07T00:00:00",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "SurgicalNumber": "",
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "896",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "MOP",
            "FirstName": "OKI",
            "MiddleName": "",
            "PatientId": "456",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/02/1968",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "123901",
            "Code": "410340",
            "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
            "LastName": "1080"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "4931",
                "Code": "1184762718",
                "FirstName": "DAVID",
                "LastName": "30159"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "J264",
                "DateCollected": "01/07/2025 06:00 AM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderedTestCode": "",
                "ParentTestCode": "",
                "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                "TestActionId_TM": 3404,
                "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                "OrderTestAnswers": [
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C309",
                        "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                        "AnswerText": "Yes",
                        "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C522",
                        "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                        "AnswerText": "> = 76 years old and total PSA > = 4 ng/mL",
                        "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C171",
                        "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                        "AnswerText": "Yes, Negative",
                        "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C169",
                        "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                        "AnswerText": "Nodule",
                        "TestName": "DRE Results",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C310",
                        "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                        "AnswerText": "76 years or older and PSA greater than 4 ng/mL",
                        "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C311",
                        "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                        "AnswerText": "Yes, the 4Kscore Test is medically reasonable and necessary for the biopsy decision.  The patient DOES NOT have factors indicating a biopsy should occur.",
                        "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C263",
                        "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                        "AnswerText": "Confirmed Persistent and Significant Rise in PSA",
                        "TestName": "Patient History",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C264",
                        "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                        "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                        "TestName": "Other",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C270",
                        "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                        "AnswerText": "YES",
                        "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C465",
                        "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                        "AnswerText": "896",
                        "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "J264"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "K135",
                "DateCollected": "01/07/2025 06:00 AM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderedTestCode": "",
                "ParentTestCode": "",
                "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                "OrderTestAnswers": [
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C309",
                        "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                        "AnswerText": "Yes",
                        "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C522",
                        "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                        "AnswerText": "> = 76 years old and total PSA > = 4 ng/mL",
                        "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C171",
                        "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                        "AnswerText": "Yes, Negative",
                        "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C169",
                        "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                        "AnswerText": "Nodule",
                        "TestName": "DRE Results",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C310",
                        "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                        "AnswerText": "76 years or older and PSA greater than 4 ng/mL",
                        "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C311",
                        "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                        "AnswerText": "Yes, the 4Kscore Test is medically reasonable and necessary for the biopsy decision.  The patient DOES NOT have factors indicating a biopsy should occur.",
                        "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C263",
                        "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                        "AnswerText": "Confirmed Persistent and Significant Rise in PSA",
                        "TestName": "Patient History",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C264",
                        "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                        "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                        "TestName": "Other",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C270",
                        "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                        "AnswerText": "YES",
                        "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    },
                    {
                        "QuestionType": 2,
                        "FormatType": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "",
                        "QuestionCode": "C465",
                        "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                        "AnswerText": "896",
                        "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                        "Condition": 1,
                        "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                        "IsTestAOE": true,
                        "GroupCode": "",
                        "TestCode": "K135"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "SpecimenID": 0,
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
        "FlaggedTests": [],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2025-01-07T09:57:46.351442-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2025-01-07T10:00:06.7412661-05:00"
    },
    "CreateOrderWithCNPD": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
                "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "OrderId": 0,
                "AccessionNumber": "-NEW-",
                "AccessioningDivision": "1",
                "AccountNumber": "J3333",
                "EReqNumber": "",
                "IsBioRequisition": true,
                "IsNamesMatch": true,
                "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
                "SpecimenCount": "1",
                "TestCount": "2",
                "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
                "DateOfCollection": "12/31/2024",
                "TimeOfCollection": "03:00 AM",
                "Priority": "ROUTINE",
                "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
                "AlternateDateCollected": "",
                "SpecimenComments": "",
                "Comments": "",
                "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
                "InitialReceivedDate": "2024-12-31T00:00:00",
                "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
                "SurgicalNumber": "",
                "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
                "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
                "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
                "OrderAnswers": [
                    {
                        "AnswerText": "139",
                        "Condition": 0,
                        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                        "Format": 13,
                        "QuestionCode": "C012",
                        "QuestionId": 12900,
                        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
                    }
                ],
                "Patient": {
                    "LastName": "ALEX",
                    "FirstName": "TRY",
                    "MiddleName": "",
                    "PatientId": "1233",
                    "Gender": "MALE",
                    "DateOfBirth": "10/05/1985",
                    "Age": "",
                    "Race": "",
                    "Ethnicity": "",
                    "IsFasting": "FASTING"
                },
                "PrimaryPhysician": {
                    "ActionType": "1",
                    "ProviderId": "125149",
                    "Code": "411475",
                    "FirstName": "TEST",
                    "LastName": "1975"
                },
                "SecondaryPhysicians": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "ProviderId": "128159",
                        "Code": "1952456477",
                        "FirstName": "GILBERTO",
                        "LastName": "ACOSTA"
                    }
                ],
                "Tests": [
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "J264",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 03:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 23525,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C309",
                                "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes",
                                "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C522",
                                "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                                "AnswerText": "55-75 years old and total PSA > = 3 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C171",
                                "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, Positive",
                                "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C169",
                                "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                                "AnswerText": "No Nodule",
                                "TestName": "DRE Results",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C310",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                                "AnswerText": "Not Provided",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C311",
                                "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                                "AnswerText": "Not provided",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C263",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED,Other",
                                "TestName": "Patient History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C264",
                                "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                                "TestName": "Other",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C270",
                                "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                                "AnswerText": "NO",
                                "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C465",
                                "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                                "AnswerText": "12",
                                "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J264"
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "OrderTestId": 0,
                        "TestCode": "J148",
                        "DateCollected": "12/31/2024 03:00 AM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                        "OrderedTestCode": "",
                        "ParentTestCode": "",
                        "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                        "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                        "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                        "TestActionId_TM": 21333,
                        "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                        "OrderTestAnswers": [
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C309",
                                "QuestionText": "Is provider signature, name and date present on the requisition? (all three required for yes)",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes",
                                "TestName": "NEED PROVIDER SIGNATURE, NAME, AND DATE",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C522",
                                "QuestionText": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test:\r\nSelecting a value below confirms that the patient had two or more elevated PSA results within the past two years. Note: The 4Kscore Test should only be ordered when medically reasonable for consideration of biopsy after excluding benign cause of PSA elevation.",
                                "AnswerText": "55-75 years old and total PSA > = 3 ng/mL",
                                "TestName": "Clinical Indication for Ordering The 4Kscore Test",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C171",
                                "QuestionText": "Prostate Biopsy History:",
                                "AnswerText": "Yes, Positive",
                                "TestName": "Biopsy History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C169",
                                "QuestionText": "DRE Result: ",
                                "AnswerText": "No Nodule",
                                "TestName": "DRE Results",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C310",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient confirmed PSA (two or more results several weeks apart)",
                                "AnswerText": "Not Provided",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT CONFIRMED PSA",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C311",
                                "QuestionText": "Is the 4Kscore Test medically reasonable and necessary for the prostate biopsy decision, or does the patient have factors that indicate a biopsy should occur no matter what the 4Kscore result is?  ",
                                "AnswerText": "Not provided",
                                "TestName": "PATIENT PROSTATE BIOPSY FACTORS",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C263",
                                "QuestionText": "Patient History (Choose all that apply)",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED,Other",
                                "TestName": "Patient History",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C264",
                                "QuestionText": "Other (Patient History):",
                                "AnswerText": "NOT PROVIDED",
                                "TestName": "Other",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C270",
                                "QuestionText": "4K test order discussed with patient? ",
                                "AnswerText": "NO",
                                "TestName": "4K Order Discussed w/Patient",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": true,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            },
                            {
                                "QuestionType": 2,
                                "FormatType": 0,
                                "DataMappingProperty": "",
                                "QuestionCode": "C465",
                                "QuestionText": "Enter UDI Barcode ",
                                "AnswerText": "12",
                                "TestName": "Enter UDI Barcode",
                                "Condition": 1,
                                "CauseDemoUpdate": false,
                                "IsTestAOE": true,
                                "GroupCode": "",
                                "TestCode": "J148"
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                ],
                "Specimens": [
                    {
                        "SpecimenID": 0,
                        "ActionType": "1",
                        "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                        "Quantity": "1",
                        "Temperature": "ROOM",
                        "IsHoldOverriden": false
                    }
                ],
                "MetaData": [
                    {
                        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                        "Value": "SingleScreen"
                    },
                    {
                        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                        "Value": "True"
                    }
                ],
                "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
                "FlaggedTests": [],
                "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00",
                "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "0001-01-01T00:00:00"
    },
    "UpdateOrderWithDOCChangeJ148LAV": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 4586864,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218148",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "12/22/2024",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
        {
        "AnswerText": "DDD",
        "Condition": 0,
        "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
        "Format": 13,
        "QuestionCode": "C012",
        "QuestionId": 12900,
        "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
        }
        ],
        "Patient": {
        "LastName": "TEST",
        "FirstName": "TEST",
        "MiddleName": "T",
        "PatientId": "123",
        "Gender": "MALE",
        "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1975",
        "Age": "",
        "Race": "",
        "Ethnicity": "",
        "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
        "ActionType": "1",
        "ProviderId": "125149",
        "Code": "411475",
        "FirstName": "TEST",
        "LastName": "1975"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
        {
        "ActionType": "1",
        "ProviderId": "123937",
        "Code": "1234567894",
        "FirstName": "MP",
        "LastName": "0322"
        }
        ],
        "Tests": [
        {
        "ActionType": "2",
        "OrderTestId": 0,
        "TestCode": "j148",
        "IsHoldOverriden": false,
        "OrderTestAnswers": []
        }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
        {
        "ActionType": "1",
        "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
        "Quantity": "1",
        "Temperature": "ROOM",
        "IsHoldOverriden": false
        }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
        {
        "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
        "Value": "SingleScreen"
        },
        {
        "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
        "Value": "True"
        }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "ChangeDateOfBirth": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 4586864,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218148",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "01/03/2025",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
            "AnswerText": "DDD",
            "Condition": 0,
            "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
            "Format": 13,
            "QuestionCode": "C012",
            "QuestionId": 12900,
            "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1965",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
            },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "125149",
            "Code": "411475",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "LastName": "1975"
            },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "123937",
            "Code": "1234567894",
            "FirstName": "MP",
            "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
            "ActionType": "2",
            "OrderTestId": 0,
            "TestCode": "j148",
            "IsHoldOverriden": false,
            "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
            "Quantity": "1",
            "Temperature": "ROOM",
            "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
            "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
            "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
            "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
            "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "UpdateTestcodeSpecimen0102LAV": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 4586864,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218148",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "01/03/2025",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "DDD",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1975",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "125149",
            "Code": "411475",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "LastName": "1975"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "123937",
                "Code": "1234567894",
                "FirstName": "MP",
                "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "2",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "0102",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "UpdateTestcodeSpecimenJ148SST" : {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 4586864,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218148",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "01/03/2025",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "DDD",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1975",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "125149",
            "Code": "411475",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "LastName": "1975"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "123937",
                "Code": "1234567894",
                "FirstName": "MP",
                "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "2",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "J148",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "RemoveTest": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 4586864,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218148",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "12/22/2024",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "DDD",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1975",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "125149",
            "Code": "411475",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "LastName": "1975"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "123937",
                "Code": "1234567894",
                "FirstName": "MP",
                "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "UpdateSpecimenJ148SST": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 4586864,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218148",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "01/03/2025",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "DDD",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1975",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "125149",
            "Code": "411475",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "LastName": "1975"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "123937",
                "Code": "1234567894",
                "FirstName": "MP",
                "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "2",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "j148",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "UpdateProviderDetails": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 4586864,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218148",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "1",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "12/22/2024",
        "TimeOfCollection": "10:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJLTJPATEL2",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "DDD",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "TEST",
            "FirstName": "TEST",
            "MiddleName": "T",
            "PatientId": "123",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "01/01/1975",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "1",
            "Code": "OTE445",
            "FirstName": "FirstName",
            "LastName": "LastName"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "123937",
                "Code": "1234567894",
                "FirstName": "MP",
                "LastName": "0322"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "2",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "j148",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "SST",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:32:03.2686383-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2024-12-11T11:33:08.2540611-05:00"
    },
    "AddingATest": {
        "ValidateOnly": true,
        "OrderSource": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "OrderId": 0,
        "AccessionNumber": "101218157",
        "AccessioningDivision": "1",
        "AccountNumber": "J3333",
        "EReqNumber": "",
        "IsBioRequisition": true,
        "IsNamesMatch": true,
        "IsTwoIDOnSpecimen": true,
        "SpecimenCount": "1",
        "TestCount": "2",
        "RequisitionType": "MANUAL_QUICK",
        "DateOfCollection": "01/03/2025",
        "TimeOfCollection": "04:00 AM",
        "Priority": "ROUTINE",
        "STATPriorityIncidentId": "",
        "AlternateDateCollected": "",
        "SpecimenComments": "",
        "Comments": "",
        "BillingType": "UNKNOWN",
        "InitialReceivedDate": "2025-01-03T00:00:00",
        "HasPhysicianSignature": true,
        "SurgicalNumber": "",
        "WorkflowType": "SINGLE_SCREEN",
        "WorkflowStep": "ALL",
        "ComputerName": "NJD1OFSRVM26",
        "OrderAnswers": [
            {
                "AnswerText": "965",
                "Condition": 0,
                "DataMappingProperty": "Order.OVOrderNumber",
                "Format": 13,
                "QuestionCode": "C012",
                "QuestionId": 12900,
                "QuestionText": "Please enter Requisition #"
            }
        ],
        "Patient": {
            "LastName": "IK",
            "FirstName": "KO",
            "MiddleName": "",
            "PatientId": "968",
            "Gender": "MALE",
            "DateOfBirth": "10/04/1964",
            "Age": "",
            "Race": "",
            "Ethnicity": "",
            "IsFasting": "FASTING"
        },
        "PrimaryPhysician": {
            "ActionType": "1",
            "ProviderId": "123901",
            "Code": "410340",
            "FirstName": "MAMATHA",
            "LastName": "1080"
        },
        "SecondaryPhysicians": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "ProviderId": "4931",
                "Code": "1184762718",
                "FirstName": "DAVID",
                "LastName": "30159"
            }
        ],
        "Tests": [
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "0034",
                "DateCollected": "01/03/2025 04:00 AM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderedTestCode": "",
                "ParentTestCode": "",
                "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            },
            {
                "ActionType": "1",
                "OrderTestId": 0,
                "TestCode": "0053",
                "DateCollected": "01/03/2025 04:00 AM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false,
                "OrderedTestCode": "",
                "ParentTestCode": "",
                "IsAutoAddOnNSR": "False",
                "AutoAddParentCode": "",
                "IsPresumptiveTest": "False",
                "TestActionId_TM": 0,
                "TestConditionId_TM": 0,
                "OrderTestAnswers": []
            }
        ],
        "Specimens": [
            {
                "SpecimenID": 0,
                "ActionType": "1",
                "SpecimenCode": "LAV",
                "Quantity": "1",
                "Temperature": "ROOM",
                "IsHoldOverriden": false
            }
        ],
        "MetaData": [
            {
                "Name": "AccessioningSystem",
                "Value": "SingleScreen"
            },
            {
                "Name": "AllowNotOrderableTests",
                "Value": "True"
            }
        ],
        "AccessionUpdateSummaries": [],
        "FlaggedTests": [],
        "AccessionCreateSessionStartDateTime": "2025-01-03T08:00:46.3180022-05:00",
        "AccessionCreateSessionEndDateTime": "2025-01-03T08:03:46.5095249-05:00"
    }
}